Nighttime and Idols
Let's go to the main project!
Mr. Harima, please give the title call.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
My three main elements
Oh!
Applause
Wait! Really!
No way!
This is not the plan!
I think this is a first.
You've never seen it arranged like this before.
I think it's also the first time to do the title call.
This time, at Mr. Takayanagi's request.
It's a Disney heroine style.
Yes.
Who was watching? Just now.
I was thinking of Cinderella.
You're Cinderella now?
I knew it. She's the center of the Disney princesses.
Well, center of center.
Center of center is Cinderella.
Cinderella starts singing when she wakes up in the morning.
I was wondering why she starts singing in the morning.
I heard Haruma's interview.
What do you mean by "Cinderella"?
There is something about the center, isn't there?
Yes, she's obsessed with the center.
That's amazing.
You know, when you talk about it...
That's right.
I think it's good.
You said it like Cinderella.
Now, Haruma-san's three main elements
From the first to the third.
Yes, sir.
Please.
First.
loud voice
Second.
Third.
persistence
But oh no! Is it like this? What's a kettle of fish?
You're a gymnast, too.
The elements that make it up. The first is loudness?
Loud.
What do you mean by that?
After all, it was at the Stapler Fest.
Loud voice challenge
Yes, yes.
And there I was,
Champion.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
So,
I have the record.
The record is already speaking for itself.
Wow.
That's why I'm here,
The numbers.
Yes, the numbers are already there.
That's right.
That's why I'm already there,
I'm confident that I can go to the Stapler festival and onward,
I feel confident that I can go on after the Stapler festival.
What are some of the good things about having a loud voice?
When I call the waiter, he comes at once.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Excuse me! I can say, "Excuse me!
When everyone sent a message.
That's right. I'm sure they will come.
I mean, I'm sure they'll come,
But generally, I think that...,
During the lesson,
When they are resting,
When other students are practicing,
I chat with them, don't I?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm usually the one who gets scolded.
I'd like to talk more secretly.
I see.
That's why I'm always saying,
"Harima, you have a big voice!" I'm always told, "Harima, you have a big voice! My friends say that.
But I am not aware of it,
I think I'm making my voice too loud.
I thought I was supposed to have the same decibel level as everyone else,
I thought, "Why should I be the only one to be upset about it?
But after the Stapla festival, I realized that I have a big voice,
I'm like, "Oh, well, I'm just a big girl.
How do you feel about this? How do you feel about that when you are on stage or in a play?
But in a play, it's the other way around,
But in a theatrical sense, it's the opposite,
How do you do that voice? I mean, how do you do your voice?
I have been praised by the director.
I am sometimes praised.
I get praised.
They often say, "Your voice looks good on stage,
I don't have to work hard to make my voice loud,
I usually call it a foot microphone,
So I usually use a foot microphone, which is a microphone attached to the stage,
So I have to ask them to pick up my voice from there.
I don't have a pin mic or anything like that.
I have to have my own voice picked up,
If you have a low voice, the microphone will not pick it up,
If you have a small voice, the microphone may not pick it up and you may not be able to reach the audience,
I can get through all the voices without freezing my throat,
I think a loud voice is strong.
I see.
I see. In your work, and in this job as well.
Yes, I see.
Do you have any problems with your loud voice?
I have a radio show,
MBS?
Yes, that's right.
I'm on MBS,
Do they ask you to stay away from the microphone?
That's the way it is.
Doesn't Mr. Miki know everything?
That's the only one who talks.
I'll go around a little more. I was told to go a little further back.
Now, that's the first time I've heard that.
They tell me every time.
So...
That's an interesting story.
Thank you.
The first one is loud
I want to go farther
I want to go out into the world
I want to fly away
Night and Idol
What do you think?
Congratulations!
There's a difference between charm and mockery.
Oh! I heard that! There's a difference between charm and mockery!
Maybe that's what the fans are looking for.
This show is about Kogezaka-san, nano-san, hy007-san
Mr. Sasagi Mayifu Yuzu Moekana,
Mr. TAKUYA
This program was sent to you courtesy of Thank you very much.